Guide to the Rice Unversity Center for Research in Parallel Computation (CRPC) records, Ken Kennedy, Scientific Director, 1989-1999 UA 125
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
Rice University Center for Research in Parallel Computation (CRPC) records, Ken Kennedy, Scientific Director
1985-1999, bulk 1990-1999
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas https://library.rice.edu/woodson
Kennedy, Ken
UA 125
39 Linear Feet (39 boxes)
This collection contains videotapes, photos, reports, and other materials associated with the operation of the Center for Research in Parallel Computation from 1985-1999.
Biographical / Historical
The Center for Research in Parallel Computation was founded by a National Science Foundation grant in 1989 with the goal of making massively parallel computing systems as usable as conventional supercomputing systems. The CRPC is a consortium of seven cores sites around the nation - Rice University, Argonne National Laboratory, Los Alamos National Laboratory, California Institute of Technology, Syracuse University, University of Tennessee, and University of Texas - as well as nine affiliated sites: Boston University, Indiana University, the Institute for Computer Applications in Science and Engineering, University of Illinoiss, University of Maryland, University of Houston, University of California, University of South California, and Drexel Unversity. More than fifty Ph.D research scientists and eighty graduate and undergraduate students participate in research programs and projects.
The CRPC in the 1990s mainly focused on five projects, two in software and three in algorithms. These included the Fortran Parallel Programming System Project, led by Ken Kennedy, scientific director of the CRPC, the Compostional Programming System project, led by Mani Chandy, the Linear Algebra Project, led by Jack Dongarra, the Optimization Project, led by John Dennis, and the Differential Equations Project, led by Andy White and Herb Keller. The CRPC also provided funding for visiting academic scientists engaged in research in related fields, led topical workshops and educational seminars throughout the year, as well as sponsored programs aimed at recruiting young students, especially women and minorities, to the realm of computer science.
Scope and Contents
This collection contains videotapes, photographs, technical reports, and other materials associated with the operation of the Center for Research on Parallel Computation from 1985 to 1999. The bulk of the material os from 1990 to 1999. The video collection, in particular, contains items ranging from instructional lectures in complex computer science to taped spots of CRPC leaders on local and national news programs. The collection also includes newspaper and online journal clippings pertaining to various CRPC projects and brochures from many CRPC events. This collection offers a look at how the CRPC grew through the 1990s to an influential, respected position in the field of computer science.
Access Restrictions
This material is open for research.
Conditions Governing Access
Stored off-site at the Library Service Center. Please request this material via woodson@rice.edu or call 713-348-2586.
Acquisition Information
This material was transferred to the Woodson Research Center, 2006.
Index Terms
Subjects
Education; Rice University -- History; College trustees; Universities and colleges
Subjects (Persons)
Kennedy, Ken; Kennedy, Ken
Subjects (Corporations)
Rice University
- Series I: Videotapes and electronic records, 1985-1998
  General note
  Included are tapes of lectures on computer science, outreach programs, and news clips related to CRPC and its personnel, as well as some CD_ROMs and floppy disks of databases. Some tapes in Beta format.
  - T-120 VHS tape, Clip of PBS KUHT "Weeknight Edition" with Ken Kennedy and Beb Burns and clip of ABC KTRK with Ken Kennedy, April 29, 1997; April 3, 1997 (Box 1, Item 1)
  - T-30 VHS tape, clip of HENAAC Award, Dr. Richard Tapia, October 12, 1996 (Box 1, Item 2)
  - T-120 VHS tape, clip of EYH '97 on ABC KTRK, April 5, 1997 (Box 1, Item 3)
  - T-30 VHS tape, clip of Richard Tapia on FOX KRIV "Hola Houston", Channel 11 "Spirit of Texas, and Channel 8 "Weeknight Edition", October 27, 1996; October 31, 1996; October 31, 1996 (Box 1, Item 4)
  - T-120 VHS tape, clip of Richard Tapia on CBS KHOU news, late 1990s (Box 1, Item 5)
  - T-120 VHS tape, clip of Girl Games Inc. on PBS KUHT "Weeknight Edition, n.d (Box 1, Item 6)
  - T-15 VHS tape, clip of Phil Gramm at Rice University on KNWS, March 14, 1997 (Box 1, Item 7)
  - T-30 VHS tape, clip of Lucille Barrerra on "Hola Houston", "HISD News Today", "Noticiero", September 29, 1996, September 3, 1996, August 27, 1996 (Box 1, Item 8)
  - T-30 VHS tape, clip of STC News Conference on CBS KHOU and ABC KTRK, December 5, 1988 (Box 1, Item 9)
  - 2 T-120 VHS tapes, CRPC PBS KUHT Membership Drive (2 copies), June 18, 1985 (Box 1, Item 10)
  - 1 Television News-Grade Beta Tape, Science and Technology Center Announcement Sound Bites, December 5, 1988 (Box 1, Item 11)
  - 1 T-120 VHS tape, Lecture on "Decision Aids for Telerobotics Command, Dr. Thomas B. Sheridan, January 23, 1989 (Box 1, Item 12)
  - 1 T-120 VHS tape, Lecture on "The Parallel Computing Era: Is it Here or is it Coming?", David Kuck, October 11, 1989 (Box 1, Item 13)
  - 1 T-120 VHS tape, Lecture on "Parallel Algorithms for Combinational Search Problems", Dr. Richard Karp, March 7, 1990 (Box 1, Item 14)
  - 1 T-120 VHS tape, lecture on "Teleoperation, Telerobotics, and Telepresence", Dr. Thomas B. Sheridan, January 24, 1989 (Box 1, Item 15)
  - 1 T-120 VHS tape, lecture on "Parallelism, Super Computing, and Computational Mathematics", Virginia Torczon, June 30, 1993 (Box 1, Item 16)
  - 1 T120 VHS tape, HENAAC lecture on "Taking Giant Steps", Richard Tapia, October 12, 1996 (Box 1, Item 17)
  - 1 T-120 VHS tape, lecture on "Building Competent Robots: Is Intelligence Enough?", Dr. Arthur C. Sanderson, February 10, 1992 (Box 1, Item 18)
  - 1 T-10 VHS tape, CITI Distinguished Lecturer J. T. Browne, November 8, 1988 (Box 1, Item 19)
  - 1 T-30 VHS tape, Sparks Exhibit, Fred Colby, 1990s (Box 1, Item 20)
  - 1 T-120 VHS tape, CRPC overview "The Creative Spark!", March 12, 1996 (Box 1, Item 21)
  - 1 T-120 VHS tape, lecture on "What's All This About Gallium Arsenide?", Seymore Cray, November 15, 1988 (Box 1, Item 22)
  - 1 T-120 VHS tape, lecture on "Telerobot Visual Language Programming Sensing and Fault-Tolerance", Dr. Larry Leifer, December 5, 1991 (Box 1, Item 23)
  - 10 CD-R74H, CRPC/Girl Games Mac Prototypes, 1996 (Box 2, Item 1)
  - 2 T-120 VHS tapes and 1 T-160 VHS tape, Discovery of Women Series Part I through Part III, March 29, 1995; April 5, 1995; April 13, 1995 (Box 2, Item 2)
  - 1 T-120 VHS tape and 1 T-30 VHS tape, Students in Science and Math (2 copies) (Box 2, Item 3)
  - 2 T-30 VHS tapes, CRPC High School Program (2 copies), n.d. (Box 2, Item 4)
  - T-120 VHS tapes, Steering Minority Education Conference (2 copies), June 25, 1988 (Box 2, Item 5)
  - 1 T-60 VHS tape, Girls' Tech, 1996 (Box 2, Item 6)
  - 1 T-60 VHS tape, "Expand Your Horizons: Math and Science", March 10, 1995 (Box 2, Item 7)
  - 11 T-120 VHS tapes, Girl Games Project, 1996 (Box 2, Item 8)
  - 1 T-120 VHS tape, Amtek Northeast Parallel Architectures Center—NII, October 19, 1994 (Box 3, Item 1)
  - 1 T-30 VHS tape, Center for Research on Parallel Computation, November 2, 1994 (Box 3, Item 2)
  - 1 T-15 VHS tape, BBN "Xtra", September 1, 1989 (Box 3, Item 3)
  - 1 T-23 VHS tape, "Super Computing '95" The Reality Shop, 1995 (Box 3, Item 4)
  - 1 T-30 VHS tape, NCSA Alliance 98, featuring Ken Kennedy, Geoffrey Fox, Rick Stevens, Dan Reed, August 11, 1998 (Box 3, Item 5)
  - 1 T-120 VHS tape, Life by the Numbers with Danny Glover, 1990s (Box 3, Item 6)
  - 1 T-30 VHS tape, The Community Services Workstation, July 22, 1991 (Box 3, Item 7)
  - 1 T-160 VHS tape and 1 T-120 VHS tape, Education on the National Information Infrastructure (NII) (2 copies), 1995 (Box 3, Item 8)
  - 2 T-15 VHS tapes and 1 T-30 Beta tape, CRPC "Parallel Computation Makes for Good Vibrations", September 20, 1995 (Box 3, Item 9)
  - 2 T-20 VHS tapes, Parallel Computing at Work, CRPC Activities in Collaboration, Knowledge Transfer, and Education (2 copies), 1990s (Box 3, Item 10)
  - 5 CD-ROMs, Personal CRAY Digital: a Tour of Supercomputing, CRAY T90 Series of Supercomputing, Universal Solutions, Science Serving Society: A Digital Montage from Los Alamos National Lab, and HyperAmp for the Macintosh (Box 3, Item 11)
  - 7 T-30 VHS tapes, NCSA Realtime (6 parts, 2 copies of #6), February 1991 (Box 3, Item 12)
  - 12 T-120 VHS tapes, Math and Computer Science Workshop Year One, 1990s (Box 4, Item 1)
  - 11 T-120 VHS tapes, Math and Computer Science Workshop, year 2, 1990s (Box 4, Item 2)
  - 2 T-120 VHS tapes, Mini-Symposium, April 12, 1989 (Box 4, Item 3)
  - 1 T-160 VHS tape, Rice Dependence Analysis Symposium, April 26-27, 1990 (Box 4, Item 4)
  - 2 T-120 VHS tapes and 1 T-20 VHS tape, Intel Grand Challenge Computing (3 copies), May 1992 (Box 4, Item 5)
  - 1 T-15 VHS tape, The Caribiner Group: IBM Golden Circle "The Cave", May 1995 (Box 4, Item 6)
  - 1 T-15 VHS tape, Intel Touchstone Delta System Dedication, May 31, 1991 (Box 4, Item 7)
  - 1 T-5 VHS Tape, Eisenhower National Clearinghouse (ENC) for Science and Mathematics Hard Drive Café, 1990s (Box 4, Item 8)
  - 1 T-30 VHS tape Amtek Series 2010 Program, February 1988 (Box 4, Item 9)
  - 10 TC-20 VHSC tapes, Math and Computer Science Workshop featuring SAS, CRPC Keith Cooper and Virginia; John Rodriguez, Emilio Ninez, and Malcolm Gillis; Dr. Leslie Miller, Rice K-8, Iris, Carl (NCTM), July 26, 1994; July 27-28, 1994; July 29, 1994 (Box 4, Item 10)
  - 1 T-120 VHS tape, Parallel Debugging and Computational Science, Part 2 Ken Kennedy, SC, 1989 (Box 5, Item 1)
  - 1 T-120 VHS tape, "Toward the Ultra High-Speed Computing System", Tadashi Watanabe, The Distinguished Lecture Series, January 31, 1992 (Box 5, Item 2)
  - 1 T-120 VHS tape, CRPC Lecture, 1990s (Box 5, Item 3)
  - 1 T-120 VHS tape, Professor Kanade, co-director of Robotic Institute Lecture (blurry), 1990s (Box 5, Item 4)
  - 1 T-120 VHS tape, Adaptive Mesh Refinement on Parallel Computers, October 22, 1993 (Box 5, Item 5)
  - 1 T-10 VHS tape, Computer Chemistry, 1990s (Box 5, Item 6)
  - 1 T-120 VHS tape, Intro to the Application Compiler, 1993 (Box 5, Item 7)
  - 1 T-120 VHS tape, Data Flow Ideas Lecture, 1990s (Box 5, Item 8)
  - 14 T-120 VHS tapes, CRPC Caltech Short Course (7 parts, 2 copies of each), January 24, 1994 (Box 5, Item 9)
  - 2 T-120 VHS tapes Computer Science Workshop Day 1: Into to SUN (2 copies), 1990s (Box 6, Item 1)
  - 2 T-120 VHS tapes, Computer Science Workshop Day 1: Intro to Unix #1 (2 copies), 1990s (Box 6, Item 2)
  - 2 T-120 VHS tapes, Computer Science Workshop Day 2: Intro to Unix #2 (2 copies), 1990s (Box 6, Item 3)
  - 2 T-120 VHS tapes, Computer Science Workshop Day 3: MatLab #1 (2 copies), 1990s (Box 6, Item 4)
  - 2 T-120 VHS tapes, Computer Science Workshop Day 3: MatLab #2 (2 copies), 1990s (Box 6, Item 5)
  - 2 T-120 VHS tapes, Computer Science Workshop Day 4: SPICE #1 (2 copies), 1990s (Box 6, Item 6)
  - 2 T-120 VHS tapes, Computer Science Workshop Day 4: SPICE #2 (2 copies), 1990s (Box 6, Item 7)
  - 1 T-120 VHS tape Computer Science Workshop Day 5: VLSI #2 (Part1), 1990s (Box 6, Item 8)
  - 1 T-120 VHS tape, Computer Science Workshop Day 6: VLSI #2, 1990s (Box 6, Item 9)
  - 1 T-120 VHS tape Computer Science Workshop Day 7: LSIM #1, 1990s (Box 6, Item 10)
  - 1 T-120 VHS tape Computer Science Workshop Day 7: LSIM #2, 1990s (Box 6, Item 11)
  - 1 T-120 VHS tape Computer Science Workshop Day 8: BDL, 1990s (Box 6, Item 12)
  - 1 T-120 VHS tape Computer Science Workshop Day 9: MAPLE #1, 1990s (Box 6, Item 13)
  - 1 T-120 VHS tape Computer Science Workshop Day 9: MAPLE #2, 1990s (Box 6, Item 14)
  - 1 T-120 VHS tape Computer Science Workshop Day 10: Networking #1, 1990s (Box 6, Item 15)
  - 1 T-120 VHS tape Computer Science Workshop Day 10: Networking #2, 1990s (Box 6, Item 16)
  - 1 T-30 VHS tape, Parallel Simulation for Enhanced Oil Recovery and Piers: The Movie, 1990s (Box 6, Item 17)
  - 1 T-20 VHS tape, Special Hydrodynamic Simulation of the Interaction of the Solar Wind with Plasma (Jet Propulsion Lab) (Box 6, Item 17)
  - 10 2HD Apple Format Floppy Disks, STC Databases Argonne, SC98 CRPC Rice University Data, SPE Staff, Girl Games, Database 4/95, Committee List, STC Syracuse, STC Database Los Mamos, Database headings, STC Database Caltech, April 1995 (Box 6, Item 18)
  - 3 T-120 VHS tapes, Basic Data for Plasma Reactor Modeling, Vince Mckoy, Caltech (3 copies), 1994 (Box 6, Item 19)
  - 1 T-120 VHS tape, Plasma Modeling-Caltech Paulette Liewer, 1990s (Box 6, Item 20)
  - 2 T-120 VHS tapes, Airshed Smog Model, 1990s (Box 6, Item 21)
  - 2 T-120 VHS tapes, Parallel Simulation for Enhanced Oil Recovery and A Waterflood Simulation Philip T. Keenan (2 copies), 1990s (Box 7, Item 1)
  - 1 T-30 Beta tape, CRPC Animation and Grix (Box 7, Item 3)
  - 1 DC 300 XL/P Data Cartridge, CITI Backup Tape STC, n.d. (Box 7, Item 4)
  - 1 T-30 Beta tape CRPC VO REEL #2, n.d. (Box 7, Item 5)
  - 3 T-30 Beta tapes, Vibration Dampening Jerry Lane, September 7, 1995 (Box 7, Item 6)
  - 1 T-10 VHS tape, Flight over Haleakala, Jet Propulsion Lab/Caltech, n.d. (Box 7, Item 7)
  - 1 T-15 VHS tape, CAVE: Argonne National Lab Drug Design Using Virtual Reality, Paul Bash, September 14, 1994 (Box 7, Item 8)
  - 2 T-120 VHS tapes, CAVE: Argonne Drug Design Using Virtual Reality, Paul Bash (2 copies), September 14, 1994 (Box 7, Item 9)
  - 1 T-120 VHS tape, CAPS weather Modeling, 1989 (Box 7, Item 10)
  - 1 T-120 VHS, Modeling of Bays and Estuaries, Mary Wheeler (Box 7, Item 11)
  - 1 T-30 Beta tape, CRPC Parallel Juggler, October 18, 1995 (Box 7, Item 12)
  - 4 T-120 VHS tapes, CRPC Parallel Juggler, October 18, 1995 (Box 7, Item 13)
- Series II: Photographs and Slides, 1990-1998
  Contains photos and slides of CRPC events, publicity photos and slides for brochures as well as many headshots of CRPC personnel.
  - 8 Photos RDSA—Theresa Chapman, April 1997 (Box 8, Item 1)
  - 5 Photos AA—Linda Torczon KUHT TV, February 1996 (Box 8, Item 2)
  - 6 Photos Board of Gov. Dinner in Martel Hall (Duncan Hall), n.d. (Box 8, Item 3)
  - 2 Photos Tapia AAAS Award, 1998 (Box 8, Item 4)
  - 2 Photos President Mentoring Award Richard A. Tapia, n.d. (Box 8, Item 5)
  - 74 Photos, 3 Negatives, and 1 Negative Sheet ADMI Conference/Awards Banquet (Box 8, Item 6)
  - 28 Photos Technical/Modeling, n.d. (Box 8, Item 7)
  - 16 Photos and 6 Negatives Tech 2005 Prints, 1995 (Box 8, Item 8)
  - 25 Photos Headshots—Visitors, n.d. (Box 8, Item 9)
  - 3 Photos Headshots—Rice University, n.d. (Box 8, Item 10)
  - 5 Photos Headshots—Argonne/UT/Caltech, n.d. (Box 8, Item 11)
  - 71 Photos and 7 Negatives Miscellaneous Promotional Photos (Box 8, Item 12)
  - 20 Photos, 9 Negatives, and 1 Program Brochure SACNAS Conference, October 10-11, 1997 (Box 9, Item 1)
  - 9 Photos and 7 Negative Sheets SYYF Prints, 1994 (Box 9, Item 2)
  - 4 Photos SIAM Prints, 1993 (Box 9, Item 3)
  - 22 Photos Panel Setup, n.d. (Box 9, Item 4)
  - 63 Photos SC Prints, 1991 (Box 9, Item 5)
  - 9 Photos and 4 Negatives SC Prints, 1992 (Box 9, Item 6)
  - 12 Photos and 2 Negatives SC 1995 San Diego Prints (Box 9, Item 7)
  - 25 Photos and 7 Negatives SC 1997 Prints (Box 9, Item 8)
  - 32 Photos Mathematical and Computational Sciences Awareness Workshop (MCSA), 1995 (Box 9, Item 9)
  - 60 Photos Mathematical and Computational Sciences Awareness Workshop (MCSA), 1995 (Box 9, Item 10)
  - 37 Photos and 10 Negatives Mathematical and Computational Sciences Awareness Workshop (MCSA), 1996 (Box 9, Item 11)
  - 4 Photos CASC, 1998 (Box 9, Item 12)
  - 4 Photos CAM, 1993 (Box 9, Item 13)
  - 10 Photos and 5 Negatives ACM, 1996 (Box 9, Item 14)
  - 4 Photos, 4 Negative Sheets, and 3 negatives AM Prints, 1996 (Box 9, Item 15)
  - 11 Photos AM Prints, 1997 (Box 9, Item 16)
  - 40 Slides South Texas Science Academy Internship Summer, 1994 (Box 10, Item 1)
  - 40 Slides "Say Yes to Youngsters' Future" Workshop, February 1994 (Box 10, Item 2)
  - 30 Slides "Say Yes to Youngsters' Future" Workshop, February 1994 (Box 10, Item 3)
  - 46 Slides "Say Yes to Youngsters' Future" Workshop, February 1994 (Box 10, Item 4)
  - 4 Negative Sheets "Say Yes to Youngsters' Future Workshop", February 1994 (Box 10, Item 5)
  - 59 Slides Study of Computer Scientists and Applied Mathematics Workshop at Rice, April 20, 1994 (Box 10, Item 6)
  - 5 Negative Sheets Study of Computer Scientists and Applied Mathematics Workshop at Rice, April 20, 1994 (Box 10, Item 7)
  - 1 Photo, 2 Negative Sheets, 7 Slides Caltech Minority Youth Program, March 21-22, 1994 (Box 10, Item 8)
  - 1 Photo, 6 Negative sheets Delft University Study Group of Computer Scientists and Applied Mathematics at Rice, April 28, 1994 (Box 10, Item 9)
  - 29 Photos, 15 Negative sheets Mathematical and Computational Sciences Awareness (MCSA) Workshop Summer, 1994 (Box 10, Item 10)
  - 55 Slides Mathematical and Computational Sciences Awareness (MCSA) Workshop Summer, 1994 (Box 10, Item 11)
  - 34 Slides, 3 Photos, 6 Negative Sheets Workshop at Rice for Teachers from the Rice School Summer, 1994 (Box 10, Item 12)
  - 15 Slides South Texas Academy Intern Program Summer, 1994 (Box 10, Item 13)
  - 21 Slides Expand Your Horizons! (Box 11, Item 1)
  - 5 Slides and 1 Negative Sheet Expand Your Horizons!, 1995 (Box 11, Item 2)
  - 40 Photos, 2 Negatives, and 2 Negative Sheets Expand Your Horizons!, 1996 (Box 11, Item 3)
  - 47 Photos and 7 Negatives SAS, 1993 (Box 11, Item 4)
  - 23 Photos Caltech Presentation Photos, n.d. (Box 11, Item 5)
  - 5 Photos Caltech Prints, 1996 (Box 11, Item 6)
  - 4 Photos and 2 Negative Sheets Caltech, 1994 (Box 11, Item 7)
  - 15 Photos Girl Tech Prints, 1995 (Box 11, Item 8)
  - 10 Photos Girl Games, 1996 (Box 11, Item 9)
  - 5 Photos Girl Tech Prints, 1996 (Box 11, Item 10)
  - 15 Photos Girl Tech Prints, 1997 (Box 11, Item 11)
  - 50 Slides Girl Tech Slides, 1997 (Box 11, Item 12)
  - 52 Slides Girl Tech Slides, 1997 (Box 11, Item 13)
  - 8 Photos and 24 Negatives Girl Tech, 1998 (Box 11, Item 14)
  - 29 Slides Red Folder, undated (Box 12, Item 1)
  - 31 Slides Red Folder #2, undated (Box 12, Item 2)
  - 32 Slides Red Folder #3, undated (Box 12, Item 3)
  - 28 Slides Red Folder #4, undated (Box 12, Item 4)
  - 38 Slides Red Folder #5, undated (Box 12, Item 5)
  - 30 Slides Red Folder #6, undated (Box 12, Item 6)
  - 39 Slides Red Folder #7, undated (Box 12, Item 7)
  - 37 Slides Red Folder #8, undated (Box 12, Item 8)
  - 35 Slides Red Folder #9, undated (Box 12, Item 9)
  - 46 Slides Computers, undated (Box 12, Item 10)
  - 38 Slides Computers, undated (Box 12, Item 11)
  - 33 Slides Computers, undated (Box 12, Item 12)
  - 25 Slides Computers, undated (Box 12, Item 13)
  - 1 Photo Model in Fortran M, undated (Box 12, Item 14)
  - 26 Photos Models, undated (Box 12, Item 15)
  - 14 Photos, 2 Negative sheets, and 32 Negatives Computer Models, undated (Box 12, Item 16)
  - 4 Photos Richard A. Tapia, undated (Box 13, Item 1)
  - 4 Photos Education Section, undated (Box 13, Item 2)
  - 7 Photos Argonne/Los Alamos, undated (Box 13, Item 3)
  - 3 Photos CSE Committee Dan Sorensen and Richard Lehoucq, undated (Box 13, Item 4)
  - 5 Photos and 1 Slide Joe Saltz and Staff, undated (Box 13, Item 5)
  - 1 Photo Education Section—Students, undated (Box 13, Item 6)
  - 2 Photos Spend a Summer with a Scientist, undated (Box 13, Item 7)
  - 1 Photo Nat McIntosh, undated (Box 13, Item 8)
  - 1 Photo CSE Opening, undated (Box 13, Item 9)
  - 15 Negatives GPCP/EC Group Shots, undated (Box 13, Item 10)
  - 30 Photos Graduate Students, undated (Box 13, Item 11)
  - 35 Photos Graduate Students, undated (Box 13, Item 12)
  - 13 Negatives Graduate Students, undated (Box 13, Item 13)
  - 2 Photos CSE Alan Weiser Reception, January 1994 (Box 13, Item 14)
  - 1 Photo and 4 Negative Sheets CSE Alan Weiser Scholarship Fall, 1993 (Box 13, Item 15)
  - 23 Photos and 1 Negative CSE Students, undated (Box 13, Item 15)
  - 19 Photos 8 Negatives, and 2 Slides CRPC Faculty and Staff, undated (Box 13, Item 16)
  - 13 Negatives and 2 Slides Faculty Researchers and Staff, January 1994 (Box 13, Item 17)
  - 8 Photos Faculty Researchers and Staff, January 1994 (Box 13, Item 18)
  - 26 Photos and 1 Slide Faculty and Staff, undated (Box 13, Item 19)
  - 15 Negatives and 8 Photos Faculty and Staff, undated (Box 13, Item 20)
  - 34 Photos Visitors, undated (Box 13, Item 21)
  - 12 Negatives Visitors, undated (Box 13, Item 22)
  - 22 Photos Guest Speakers, undated (Box 13, Item 23)
  - 22 Negatives Faculty and Staff, January 1994 (Box 13, Item 24)
  - 19 Negatives and 4 Photos Faculty and Staff, undated (Box 13, Item 25)
  - 21 Slides Faculty and Staff, undated (Box 13, Item 26)
  - 9 Negatives Guest Speakers, undated (Box 13, Item 27)
  - 6 Photos Don Heller, visitor Shell Development, Spring 1994 (Box 13, Item 28)
  - 17 Slides Outreach Faculty and Staff, undated (Box 13, Item 29)
  - 40 Photos Supercomputing, 1990 (Box 14, Item 1)
  - 43 Photos Supercomputing, 1990 (Box 14, Item 2)
  - 49 Photos Supercomputing, 1990 (Box 14, Item 3)
  - 21 Negatives Supercomputing, 1990 (Box 14, Item 4)
  - 37 Photos Supercomputing, 1991 (Box 14, Item 5)
  - 40 Photos Supercomputing, 1991 (Box 14, Item 6)
  - 13 Photos Supercomputing, 1991 (Box 14, Item 7)
  - 8 Negatives Supercomputing, 1991 (Box 14, Item 8)
  - 7 Photos Supercomputing, 1993 (Box 14, Item 9)
  - 14 Photos Out-of-State Conference, undated (Box 14, Item 10)
  - 6 Negatives Out-of-State Conference, undated (Box 14, Item 11)
  - 40 Photos Supercomputing, 1994 (Box 14, Item 12)
  - 27 Photos Supercomputing, 1994 (Box 14, Item 13)
  - 22 Negatives Supercomputing, 1994 (Box 14, Item 14)
  - 30 Photos LANL Research Symposium, 1991 (Box 14, Item 15)
  - 10 Negatives LANL Research Symposium, 1991 (Box 14, Item 16)
  - 15 Photos Rice Research Symposium, November 1993 (Box 14, Item 17)
  - 12 Photos Caltech Meeting, January 24-27, 1994 (Box 14, Item 18)
  - 11 Photos and 6 Negatives Domain Decomposition, March 1991 (Box 14, Item 19)
  - Photos and 9 Negatives Partnerships in Computer Science, January 1992 (Box 14, Item 20)
  - 18 Photos and 5 Negatives ICS, July 1992 (Box 14, Item 21)
  - 6 Photos GPCP Affiliates Meeting, August 1992 (Box 14, Item 22)
  - 26 Photos GPCP/FPMPP Corporate Affiliates Meeting, June 29, 1993 (Box 14, Item 23)
  - 10 Negatives GPCP/FPMPP Corporate Affiliates Meeting, June 29, 1993 (Box 14, Item 24)
  - 8 Photos FPMPP Corporate Affiliates Meeting, 1993 (Box 14, Item 25)
  - 8 Negative Sheets Subsurface Modeling Group Corporate Affiliates, 1994 (Box 14, Item 26)
  - 29 Slides Subsurface Modeling Group Corporate Affiliates, 1994 (Box 14, Item 27)
  - 22 Photos HPFF Meetings, 1992 (Box 14, Item 28)
  - 11 Photos HPFF II Meeting, April 6-8, 1994 (Box 14, Item 29)
  - 3 Photos and 3 Negatives Staff Meeting, undated (Box 14, Item 30)
  - 13 Photos and 4 Negatives Traveling Salesman Problem Workshop, April 1990 (Box 14, Item 31)
  - 8 Negative Sheets CITI Seminar Rice News, February 1993 (Box 14, Item 32)
  - 3 Photos SIAM Geosciences Meeting, April 19-21, 1993 (Box 14, Item 33)
  - 34 Pictures and 1 slide NSF Education Brochure, undated (Box 15, Item 1)
  - 18 Photos NSF Education Brochure, undated (Box 15, Item 2)
  - 8 Photos NSF Education Brochure, undated (Box 15, Item 3)
  - 3 Photos and 1 Slide Syracuse Brochure with Daniel Bauman, undated (Box 15, Item 4)
  - 42 Photos Caltech Minority Youth Program, March 1993 (Box 15, Item 5)
  - 13 Negative Sheets 1994 Caltech Minority Youth Program (Box 15, Item 6)